// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Who invented C++?",
  answer: "d) Bjarne Stroustrup",
  options: [
    "a) Dennis Ritchie",
    "b) Ken Thompson",
    "c) Brian Kernighan",
    "d) Bjarne Stroustrup"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of the following approach is used by C++??",
  answer: "c) Bottom-up",
  options: [
    "a) Left-right",
    "b) Right-left",
    "c) Bottom-up",
    "d) Top-down"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++??",
  answer: "d) Friend constructor",
  options: [
    "a) Default constructor",
    "b) Parameterized constructor",
    "c) Copy constructor",
    "d) Friend constructor"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " What is abstract class in C++?",
  answer: "d) Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one pure virtual functions",
  options: [
    "a) Any Class in C++ is an abstract class",
    "b) Class from which any class is derived",
    "c) Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one virtual functions",
    "d) Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one pure virtual functions"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: " By default, all the files in C++ are opened in _________ mode.",
  answer: "c) Text",
  options: [
    "a) Binary",
    "b) b) VTC",
    "c) Text",
    "d) ISCII"
  ]
},
{
numb: 6,
  question: "  Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions?",
  answer: "d) call by reference",
  options: [
    "a) call by object",
    "b) call by pointer",
    "c) call by value",
    "d) call by reference"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7,
  question: " What is Inheritance in C++?",
  answer: "a) Deriving new classes from existing classes",
  options: [
    "a) Deriving new classes from existing classes",
    "b) Overloading of classes",
    "c) Classes with same names",
    "d) Wrapping of data into a single class"
  ]
},{
numb: 8,
  question: " Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?",
  answer: "d) bool",
  options: [
    "a) double",
    "b) anonymous",
    "c) int",
    "d) bool"
  ]
},
{
numb: 9,
  question: " Which concept allows you to reuse the written code in C++?",
  answer: "a) Inheritance",
  options: [
    "a) Inheritance",
    "b) Polymorphism",
    "c) Abstraction",
    "d) Encapsulation"
  ]
},
{
numb: 10,
  question: " What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?",
  answer: "c) class having many forms",
  options: [
    "a) class having only single form",
    "b) class having four forms",
    "c) class having many forms",
    "d) class having two forms"
  ]
},


];